Talking about spiritual stocks, my
first stock will be here. I like these stocks very
much. Your channel Parvez
Avail has commented. I still have
many reasons to be very positive. First of all, the way the IT sector is doing
fitness and multi-
year growth, this will be one of the biggest benefits for it.
Because the
way Infosys has established itself here,
they have created a folder here, there are
very good margins from there and the
best thing is that whenever they give guidance, they are
revising the sites again and again.
You become more confident on the website.
This was that the margin guidance should be
revised well. If there is a problem with 2123 to
24, then you are better off with this. On the
other hand, revenue guidance
because unless there is an increase in usage, the
bottom line will not be maintained and the pack will not achieve good
growth. So in the revenue guidance,
they have backed it up here on your side by
about 2.5 to 252
percent. And I
find the movie very positive. Beans which  That
here the company consistently earns, so
when he became the PM, he had the biggest
breakthrough here, around $7 billion in the last quarter,
these days are tired
and till now, if we look at the 21st year of our career, then
2018 is gas, there will be
no extra revenue for Avni, it will keep
growing seriously, it will keep growing, the margins will keep
increasing, so I like Infosys very much,
for the long term my
target here is 17, from the long term, if there will be a
Chunaria here, then you can take it for one year also, that is, don't
start with Infosys ITC giant and it is absolutely a laptop, I am getting a
good thing in front, see
in the middle of this trend and many people say
that the expectations of growth for the next 10 years have been
advanced due to the
digital edition in 2030, as much as you talked about in Twenty20,
so you can imagine how much the picture
of this industry will change by 2030,
but yes, Infosys will have a better start at
this time.  1717 means that at this time this stock
is standing, from there you can send the app ID to 3235,
but the name Good Luck is given so that you do
not have to worry much, keep on this topic,
start trading in stocks,
through whichever brokers, through whichever online
you approach, all of them give
you options for typing in stocks,
at the beginning of every month, whatever money you have, you have to buy
one share from you, take 556, take 10106,
you keep doing this every fortnightly, every minister, keep doing it one
plate, eventually good returns will be
given, so dip it again, artificial,
very good stretchy because I will
pick up the office phone, you will drink the tips, then you have to
buy, do not be afraid, you will
see good returns from them here, long
gown problem has started, Infosys
is definitely with us, Rakesh, next
which such app you should come to the next stop in this piggy bank, in
City mode, I told
my total staff of SBI there, I
believe that the benefits, the results that came in the last two quarters,
people should also have a
clear interaction with that.  The stocks of PSU banks which had become
extinct are coming back in the city. The
problems in SBI are in spite of that
despite all the cooperative banks and private banks, after coming in the above, the chairman
secretary and even after landing, you have to
maintain your face that the positive
science, to focus from the last point, you can
click on 15 percent from retail loan and gold loan, that if I had gone into details, it would have seemed like the
big accounts would have been melted,
there you would have seen
Bank of India being the biggest bank
and especially the confidence of this is that there is a huge
acidity in SBI, but if we have
given such numbers to it, then many people are
comparing it with private sector banks, that is why you are seeing such a
jump and that is why they are saying
that brother, it is not there, I am
preparing for SBI to go up to 500,
but this is true, this week we have
seen very good results in banking stocks, so
enter into SIP mode in it, from 5.30 pm onwards,
where it is standing in the box, the
stock is also at 35 to 40.  Cent is
preparing to go up further, so this is the second
after Infosys, which is going to go into your piggy bank,
similar in free mode Amritsar Douglas,
who is this Infosys after SBI, when
my fourth add people, this
is a private sector leader in general insurance and
if you look at its result notification result,
female adoption was quite good, Kamleshwar did it
perfectly because the income of clean savers
who drank breast milk,
they bought 9% good
in the last quarter and we are looking at it
that Saurabh Giri has come down by 40%, who has done fire engineering from the center,
he has also done a very
despicable act and if this is done by drinking juice by 2030, as soon as possible
[music], as soon as possible in the
next one year
in any topic, then this 3 to 5 year
time take
130 plateau Ashok is visible, that is, 20
to 25 percent when side from the current levels,
but if we wait for three to five years, then there are
other ways from here, by
which he will be seen doing poetry and anyway  It is being
said that the flavour of insurance should be included
in your portfolio.
In the rural country, there is an inch and extra.
Generally, life is this. Now let's talk about your
skin online general insurance company
ICICI Lombard.
SBI is also infallible in the problem of buying. Good luck.
Infosys has come in this and even after that
ICICI people have come three times. I will
wrap up later. So let me move my mind forward.
What is the next topic after Amritsar ICICI Lombard and this topic is
NTPC. Its entire site is Power
Grid Corporation and people think that
its address position school is
Addison-Wesley. It goes on hydraulics and
no one else's.
[Music]
A message to Delhi 133 and in this 330 is of the
Sangh and the next big thing in power is
gold. Also news on 14th and subscribe.
Like and subscribe and
that 24 was a little big record on this channel.
Unification record and service you
next tax of 40% is visible from here.
For piggy bank, click for long time and
which stock is quite  They haven't been running for a long time, for
example, ITC, SBI, all of them
started to gain momentum, NTPC has also been in the ascendancy for a long time, so
Ghaghra's momentum will pick up. Let
us talk about which one,
Mehra, the clerk, was
also a wanderer, who performed quite well,
and I believe that Meghnad used to be a
good student today, he also got success, so
apart from this, there is one more thing that whatever is
written, there is a momentum going on, after 2 minutes, I already
share it in the second one,
I think that after looking at their
percentage, you can get relief and you are
definitely preparing, you should
start with it, and the last one will be
yours after Infosys, and it is quite enough that I
feel that there are a lot of missions in it,
because of this it was good, and the biggest thing here
I have mentioned is One India, in which
this point is in the form of channel subscription, so
what will happen from this, this was a unique achievement,
Lord Distribution will
get a lot of support, so this is the stage, I think
that yours will play well, on the other hand,
their product was launched, something  Time ago, the
exit from the inhaler is gaining a lot of
traction here. That stick, the
shower, play the game here. The fourth question
mark is there, but it has already done it. It seems
that going forward, it will increase the insurance patient by up to 20%. There is a lot of
demand in the USA as well. So, this product is
working very well for consumption here. On the other
hand, management or Aero should do a strategic approach that whatever
related products are there in their portfolio, they are
gradually shifting from here to graduate to
aspect related products and right now they are doing a lot
on buggy. If we
talk about pain, that also seems to be a very good
strategy. And as per my opinion,
going forward, the contingency on the companies will be
good. And that is why, as much as we
like here, I would like to put 1110. The
profit has already started and that too is quite high
in the market. It was
time to present these sites to our village with the officer CID. We have to
sit on the India story, we have to invest,
but Tiger should also make a judgment.
Cipla is on your screens.  The annual
target is 30% offside but I am
telling you this again and again that
in the coming few months I am brining it that
I will see you giving even better literature from here
in the coming years, let's go
Gullak is ready, what has been done
in this, good luck, one of its customers will
come on your screen, there is SBI in branch,
ICICI Lombard in functions, after that
we talked about IIT, in this
you saw the flavour of the giant Infosys and
in Tonnes, MLA in power, NTPC and finally
Cipla in pharma, so what,
this country is filled with good diversified problem stocks, if
you stuff them completely in it then
in the coming time
you will also become a good decorator